<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<stratosEula>
    <Header>End User License Agreement</Header>
    <EULA>WSO2 Cloud Commercial Terms of Use

GENERAL CONDITIONS

WSO2, Inc. (hereinafter "WSO2") provides WSO2 Cloud, (which term includes all WSO2 public cloud offerings that WSO2 may now or hereinafter introduce as part of WSO2 Cloud, a current list of which can be found at http://wso2.com/Cloud, (hereinafter "WSO2 Cloud") to you (either an individual or a single entity) subject to these Terms of Use, the terms of use generally applicable to the use of our website and services - http://wso2.com/, (the "Website") at http://wso2.com/terms-of-use and the WSO2 Cloud Service Level Agreement (SLA) at http://wso2.com/cloud/sla-support/ (hereinafter collectively referred to as the "Terms"). Your use of this Website and WSO2 Cloud shall be deemed Your acceptance of the Terms. These Terms contain the sole and entire agreement of the parties pertaining to the use of WSO2 Cloud and WSO2 has the right to suspend or terminate and refuse any and all current or future use of WSO2  Cloud (or any portion thereof) in the event of any non-compliance. These Terms may be updated by WSO2. You understand and agree that you are solely responsible for reviewing these Terms from time to time. You can always review the most current version of these Terms at http://wso2.com/cloud/terms-of-use. Any continued use of WSO2 Cloud by you after such amended Terms have been posted or information regarding such amendment has been sent to you, shall be deemed your consent and agreement to such amended Terms. You agree that, regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of WSO2 Cloud or these Terms must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. These Terms do not create any joint venture, partnership, agency, or employment relationship between the parties, although WSO2 reserves the right to name you as a user of WSO2 Cloud. The provisions governing Warranty Disclaimer, Limitation of Liability AND Indemnity, Intellectual Property Rights, Pricing and Payments will survive termination or expiration of these Terms. The section titles in these Terms are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.

END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT FOR WSO2 CLOUD AND RESTRICTIONS

WSO2 hereby provides you with a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable and terminable license to access and use WSO2 Cloud solely for your operations. No rights with respect to WSO2 Cloud are granted to you other than those specifically detailed in these Terms. WSO2 reserves the right to refuse connections/traffic/users beyond the contracted subscription tier. You acknowledge and agree that WSO2 owns all right, title and interest (including without limitation all patents, copyrights, trade secrets or other proprietary rights) in WSO2 Cloud, and any modifications, corrections or enhancements thereto, whether or not made by WSO2. You further acknowledge that WSO2 Cloud contains valuable trade secrets and confidential information of WSO2, including but not limited to the specifications, functionality and performance thereof, and you shall take all reasonable precautions to prevent any disclosure of such information except as expressly permitted in these Terms. WSO2 shall host WSO2 Cloud and may upgrade the functionality and user interface of WSO2 Cloud from time to time in its sole discretion and in accordance with these Terms. You acknowledge that such upgrades may result in changes to the appearance and/or functionality of WSO2 Cloud. You agree that your purchases hereunder are neither contingent on the delivery of any future functionality or features nor dependent on any oral or written public comments made by us regarding future functionality or features. These Terms shall also apply to any modules or features subsequently provided by WSO2 to you, and/or that have been purchased by you from WSO2 that augment or enhance WSO2  Cloud. You understand that the technical processing and transmission of WSO2  Cloud, including your information, may involve (a) transmissions over various networks; and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices. For the purposes of these Terms, content shall include any and all data, text, software, documents and other materials you may upload pursuant to your use of WSO2 Cloud and the Website (the "Content"). The Content that you upload, post or otherwise transmit via your use of WSO2 Cloud and the Website and is publicly visible to WSO2 Website users and other users of WSO2 Cloud(including, without limitation, any Content submitted to any message boards) or modifications you may make to the Content (collectively, "Publicly Visible User Content") is owned by you and subject to our privacy policy at http://wso2.com/privacy-policy/. WSO2 does not claim ownership of the Publicly Visible User Content and shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such Content, in each case except to the extent expressly assumed under written agreement. You hereby grant WSO2 and  its Affiliates,  a worldwide, royalty-free, paid-up, transferable, sublicensable, non-exclusive license to use, reproduce, modify, distribute, transmit, display, perform, adapt, and publish any Content including Publicly Visible User Content for the purposes of: formatting, maintenance, repair, protection, organization, or other administration of the Website and for the use of such Content in the course of WSO2's provision of the Website or WSO2 Cloud and any related services. This license will remain in effect until such Content is removed from the Website. You hereby represent and warrant that you have proper authorization for the worldwide transfer and processing among WSO2, its Affiliates, and third-party providers of any information or Content you create or provide and are in compliance with all laws relating to software or data export. As used in these Terms, "Affiliate" means any entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with WSO2.

Restrictions

The license granted in these Terms and your use of WSO2 Cloud shall not include outsourcing, renting or time-sharing of WSO2  Cloud.
You may not (and you may not permit anyone else to): (a) copy, modify, create a derivative work of, reverse engineer, decompile or otherwise attempt to extract the source code of WSO2 Cloud or any part thereof, unless this is expressly permitted or required by law, or unless you have been specifically told that you may do so in writing (e.g., through an open source software license); or (b) attempt to disable or circumvent any security mechanisms used by or is running on WSO2 Cloud.
You also specifically agree not to use the WSO2  Cloud, the Website or Content in any way which violates or infringes anyone's intellectual property rights; transmits software viruses or any other computer code, files, or programs designed to interrupt, destroy, or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment; or which is in any other way harmful to WSO2 its Affiliates, or other users of WSO2 Cloud, the Website or Content, or is illegal or unlawful in any manner.
You agree that the license granted herein is not a concurrent user license.
You are expressly prohibited from sublicensing use of WSO2 Cloud to any third parties. You agree that WSO2 shall own all rights, title and interest in and to all intellectual property rights in WSO2 Cloud. Except as provided in these Terms, the license granted to you does not convey any rights in WSO2 Cloud, expressed or implied, or ownership in WSO2 Cloud or any intellectual property rights thereto. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by WSO2.
Upon written approval from WSO2, you may conduct load or performance tests on WSO2 Cloud provided that when doing so you remain within your purchased subscription tier.
You may not use WSO2 Cloud if you are a person or entity barred from receiving WSO2 Cloud services under the laws of the United States or any other country, including the country you are resident in, or from which you use WSO2 Cloud.

Customer Support

You will be responsible for receiving and responding to all calls for support from your end users for WSO2 Cloud and for performing initial problem analysis, diagnosis, and replication of the problem at your location. Problems will be deemed replicated if they occur persistently, if it seems reasonably likely they originate in WSO2 Cloud, and if you reasonably cooperate with WSO2 by providing logs and other information about the problem, its occurrences, and provide assistance to WSO2 to help isolate the problem. WSO2 provides online and email technical support through the Help/Contact Support menu in the relevant WSO2 Cloud user interface. If for any reason this menu is not available, you may contact WSO2 support by e-mail at the following address: cloud@wso2.com. In order for WSO2 to process your support request, you shall: (a) identify yourself and the service affected, (b) describe the nature of the outage; and (c) provide contact information in the form of email for follow up communications.
Exceptions: WSO2 has no obligation to provide support services for problems in the operation or performance of WSO2 Cloud caused by a non-WSO2 software or hardware product.

PRICING AND PAYMENT

WSO2 Cloud pricing and payment plans are available at http://wso2.com/cloud/pricing. Fees are nonrefundable and billed monthly in advance or yearly in advance, at your option,. Your subscription period commences on the first day you access WSO2  Cloud on the basis of a paying account. You will be automatically charged in terms of the credit card or shall receive an invoice based on the billing information provided by you once WSO2 generates the invoice for the usage plan You have subscribed for. If you exceed the subscribed usage plan you will be charged for such excessive usage in accordance with WSO2’s records of your usage data and WSO2 will invoice you accordingly on the next billing cycle. You will not receive prior notification of your excessive usage or of the proportionate increase that will be reflected in your next invoice. Upgrade of a subscription plan will be made effective immediately but cancellations and downgrades will be made effective from the next billing cycle; accordingly no refunds will be offered. You will be issued with receipts for payments made. All fees are exclusive of any applicable Taxes. You will pay to WSO2 an amount equal to any Taxes arising from or relating to these Terms, including without limitation, sales, service, use or value added taxes, which are paid by or are payable by WSO2.
"Taxes" means any form of taxation, levy, duty, customs fee, charge, contribution or impost of whatever nature and by whatever authority imposed (including without limitation any fine, penalty, surcharge or interest), excluding, however, any taxes based solely on the net income of WSO2. If you are required under any applicable law or regulation, domestic or foreign, to withhold or deduct any portion of the payments due to WSO2, then the sum payable to WSO2 will be increased by the amount necessary so that WSO2 receives an amount equal to the sum it would have received had you made no withholdings or deductions.
WSO2 reserves the right to change list prices and pricing plans in line with periodic scheduled price revisions and in the event that WSO2 is of the view that such a change may adversely affect the plan you have subscribed you will receive thirty (30) days prior notice by e-mail of the proposed change.

Transaction History: unless your account has been disabled by WSO2 or otherwise, you will be able to access to your monetary transactions relating to WSO2 Cloud by logging in to the system with your access username and password.

CUSTOMER REGISTRATION

In order to receive services in relation to WSO2 Cloud you must complete the WSO2 registration process subject to the user restrictions detailed at http://wso2.com/terms-of-use.

PUBLICITY

You agree that you will display the "Powered by WSO2  Cloud" logo on any stores powered by WSO2 Cloud. You agree that as long as these Terms remain in force, WSO2 may issue press releases and orally make reference to the fact that you are a customer of WSO2. WSO2 agrees that you may, as long as these Terms remain in force, also make reference, orally or in writing, that WSO2 is one of your service providers. WSO2 reserves the right to use your web services description to configure examples in its press releases, marketing channels and any other publicity materials as well as the right to link to your site.

INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS

All right, title, and interest in and to WSO2 Cloud and all intellectual property rights in the foregoing will remain vested in WSO2. Neither party will at any time do, permit or cause to be done, any act or thing that would tend to impair or dilute in your case, WSO2’s rights in WSO2 Cloud or either party’s trademarks, service marks, and trade names. You acknowledge and agree that WSO2 may use aggregate data derived from your use of WSO2 Cloud hereunder subject to our privacy policy at http://wso2.com/privacy-policy/

TERMINATION

You agree that WSO2 at its sole discretion, has the right (but not the obligation) to delete or deactivate your account, block your email or IP address, or otherwise terminate your access to or use of WSO2  Cloud (or any part thereof), immediately and without notice, and remove and discard any User Content within the Website, for any reason, including, without limitation, if WSO2 believes that you have acted inconsistently with these Terms. Further, you agree that WSO2 shall not be liable to you or any third-party for any termination of such access to the Website. Further, you agree not to attempt to use WSO2  Cloud after said termination. You may terminate your account using the billing user interface at any point in time upon notification to WSO2. Upon termination of your account, access will cease immediately and WSO2 may remove, delete, or disable Content, account and transaction history, or any other material associated with your account at WSO2  Cloud, at its sole convenience. No termination of these Terms will affect any obligation to make payment of outstanding amounts owed by you to WSO2. WSO2 reserves the right at any time and from time to time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, WSO2 Cloud (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree that WSO2 shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of WSO2 Cloud.

WARRANTY DISCLAIMER, LIMITATION OF LIABILITY AND INDEMNITY

Your use of WSO2 Cloud will be subject to the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations detailed at http://wso2.com/terms-of-use. WSO2 does not provide any warranty as to your use of third-party content, software or services that you obtain via WSO2 Cloud. YOU HEREBY AGREE, AT YOUR EXPENSE, TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND AND HOLD WSO2 HARMLESS FROM AND AGAINST ANY LOSS, COST, DAMAGES, LIABILITY, AND/OR EXPENSE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO (A) THIRD PARTY CLAIMS, ACTIONS OR ALLEGATIONS OF INFRINGEMENT BASED ON INFORMATION, DATA OR CONTENT YOU SUBMITTED IN CONNECTION WITH WSO2 CLOUD, (B) ANY FRAUD, MANIPULATION OR OTHER BREACH OF THESE TERMS BY YOU, OR (C) THIRD PARTY CLAIMS, ACTIONS OR ALLEGATIONS BROUGHT AGAINST WSO2 ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF WSO2  CLOUD.
    </EULA>
</stratosEula>
